<Publish>
	<ModId Value="152153" />
	<DisplayName Value="Concurrent Bus Boarding" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Let multiple buses board and unload together at the same stop, with automatic and editable boarding zones." />
	<LongDescription>
Concurrent Bus Boarding lets several buses use the same stop at the same time when there is enough road space. The stop is the forward edge of the boarding zone, buses queue naturally behind it, board and unload concurrently, then continue to their next stop when finished.

FEATURES

- Up to two buses board together at ordinary curbside stops.
- Pull-in bays use their full detected lane and fit as many buses as their usable length allows.
- Buses keep their natural traffic spacing and remain stopped once boarding starts, even when the bus ahead leaves.
- Waiting passengers are offered to active buses in round-robin order while the game keeps its normal route, fare, animation, and capacity checks.
- Every served bus stop has a length control plus draggable rear-edge map handles for resizing its boarding zone.
- Per-stop edits save with the city and can be reset to automatic detection at any time.
- Options includes a confirmed action that resets every customized zone in the current city.
- Boarding-zone overlays show only for the selected stop by default; this can be changed in Options.

HOW TO EDIT A STOP

Select a served bus stop and open Bus Boarding Zone. Use Length for precise adjustment, or choose Edit on map and drag either cyan rear corner. The stop remains the fixed forward edge. Right-click or press Escape when finished.

SCOPE AND COMPATIBILITY

Only passenger buses are changed. Other public transport and cargo vehicles keep their normal behaviour. This is a code mod that integrates with the game's vehicle and passenger ECS systems; it may require an update after a major game patch.
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/concurrent-boarding.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/pull-in-queue.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/selected-stop-setting.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/custom-zone-controls.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/map-editing-handles.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.2.0" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.0*" />
	<ChangeLog Value="Hardens native and managed boarding lifecycles, validates route and zone data before use, and shows mod errors in the in-game error UI. Waiting passengers now retry buses behind a full lead bus, eligible buses no longer skip their target stop, and Options includes a confirmed action to reset every customized zone in the current city." />
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/mod-concurrent-bus-boarding-allow-several-buses-use-the-same-stop-at-the-same-time.1935925/" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Meapy/concurrent-bus-boarding" />
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
